Guide to the Virginia Nelson playbills collection, 1939-2007
George Mason University Libraries
  - The Studio Theatre - "Sylvia,", March 12, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - U.S. Navy Memorial Theatre - "Love Notes,", April 14, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - The Old Vat Theatre - "The Old Bull and Bush,", April 23, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - The Studio Theatre - "Love! Valor! Compassion!,", April 30, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - The Shakespeare Theatre - "Sweet Bird of Youth,", May 26, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - The Little Theatre of Alexandria - "Crazy For You,", July 18, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Woolly Mammoth Theatre Co. - "Brimstone and Treacle,", October 27, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Adelphi Theatre - "Chicago,", November 18, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - The Studio Theatre - "Miss Margarida's Way,", December 17, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Ryman Auditorium - "Always...Patsy Cline,", 1998 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Woolly Mammoth Theatre Co. - "The Gene Pool,", January 12, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Warner Theatre - "Defending the Caveman,", March 1998 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - The National Theatre - "Ragtime,", April 1998 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - America Dancing, April 1998 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - George Mason University Concert Hall for the Arts - Universal Ballet with Korea's Prime Philharmonic, April 11, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Cort Theatre - "Freak" - John Leguizamo, May 1998 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - St. James Theatre - "High Society,", May 1998 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Signature Theatre - "You're Gonna Love Tomorrow,", May 26, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Krapp's Last Tape,", June 1998 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - The Interact Theatre Co. - "Great Expectations,", August 5, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - The Shakespeare Theatre - "A Woman of No Importance,", September 1, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Arts Club of Washington - "The Telephone,", November 20, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - The Studio Theatre - "The Vagina Monologues,", November 28, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Wolf Trap - Kathy Mattea and Collin Raye, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Houston Gran Opera - "Aida,", 1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Annie Get Your Gun," Featuring Bernadette Peters, January 1999 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - John Golden Theatre - "Side Man," Featuring Edie Falco, Christina Slater, March 1999 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - The Studio Theatre - "The Beauty Queen of Leenane,", March 10, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Ford's Theatre - "Eleanor: An American Love Story,", March 10, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Theatre Royal Haymarket - "The Prisoner of Second Avenue," Featuring Marsha Mason and Richard Dreyfuss, March 22, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Folger Theatre - "The Dresser,", April 2, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - The In Series - A Noel and Cole Cabaret, April 16, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Gate Theatre - "Artistocrats,", May 4, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Red White and Tuna,", June 1999 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Titanic,", July 1999 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "The Whiteheaded Boy,", September 1999 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Woolly Mammoth Theatre Co. - "The Dead Monkey,", October 1999 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Masters of 20th Century Ballet, October 21, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Martin Guerre,", December 1999 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Ford's Theatre - Barbara Cook - A Broadway Evening, circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - The Church Street Theatre - An Evening with Quentin Crisp, circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Ford's Theatre - "Balletap USA,", circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Ford's Theatre - "The Foreigner,", circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - American Playwrights Theatre - "Briktop,", circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - GW's Lisner Auditorium - Ute Lemper in Concert, circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - The Washington Stage Guild - "Anatol,", circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Edward Albee, circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Mandy Patinkin In Concert, circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - The Studio Theatre - "Laughing Wild,", circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Casa Blanca de Buenos Aires - "Los Mejores,", circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Round House Theatre - "Tintypes,", circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - "A Tuna Christmas,", circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Washington Shakespeare Company - "The Importance of Being Oscar,", circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Wit," Featuring Judith Light, February 29, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Houston Ballet, Featuring Carlos Acosta, March 2000 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - The Studio Theatre - "Betty's Summer Vacation,", March 7, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Warner Theatre - Foot Notes - The Concert, March 25, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - The Booth Theatre - "Dame Edna,", June 2000 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "The Dinner Party," Featuring Henry Winkler, July 2000 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Balanchine Celebration, September 2000 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - True Note Productions - "From The Heart,", September 30, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - GW'S Lisner Auditorium - Ute Lemper, October 14, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - National Theatre - "Fosse,", December 2000 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - The Playwrights Forum - An Evening of Original Holiday Songs, December 11, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Theatre J - DCJCC - 2001-2002 Schedule, circa 2001 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Ethel Barrymore Theatre - "The Tale of the Allergist's Wife,", January 2001 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Ford's Theatre - "Fully Committed', February 2001 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - The Studio Theatre - "The Invention of Love,", March 28, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Mill on the Floss,", May 16, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Lulu," Featuring Anna Friel, June 16, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Kiss Me, Kate,", July 3, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Phoenix Productions - "Late Night Catechism,", July 10, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Theatre J - DCJCC - "The People's Violin,", November 1, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Dirty Blonde,", December 12, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - The Santa Fe Opera Schedule, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Signature Theatre - "The Gospel According to Fisher,", January 8, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - National Theatre - "Contact,", February 2002 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Copenhagen,", February 26, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Hexagon - "It's A Grand Old Gag,", February 28, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Neil Simon Theatre - Elaine Stritch - At Liberty, March 2002 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - The Studio Theatre - "Prometheus,", March 20, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - National Theatre - "Mamma Mia!,", April 2002 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Theatre J - DCJCC - "Born Guilty,", May 19, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - The Mead Theatre - "Lypsinka!,", June 14, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - The Santa Fe Opera Schedule, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Signature Theatre - "The Christmas Carol Rag,", November 12, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - National Theatre - "Dame Edna,", January 2003 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Theatre J - DCJCC - "The Last Seder,", January 8, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - The Shakespeare Theatre - "The Silent Woman,", January 21, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Signature Theatre - "Follies,", April 1, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - The Catholic University of America - "Radium Girls,", April 9, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Theatre J - DCJCC - "The Mad Dancers,", April 29, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Barbara Cook In Concert, June 2003 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - The Studio Theatre - "Lackawanna Blues,", June 6, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Theatre J - DCJCC - "Talley's Folly,", June 18, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Woolly Mammoth Theatre Co. - "The Mineola Twins,", August 25, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Olney Theatre - "Piaf,", October 7, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Bounce,", October 21, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - The Washington Opera - "Die Walkure," Featuring Placido Domingo, November 5, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Broadhurst Theatre - "Never Gonna Dance,", December 2003 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Radio City Music Hall - Christmas Spectacular, circa December 2003 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Al Hirschfeld Theatre - "Wonderful Town," Featuring Donna Murphy and Jennifer Westfeldt, December 2003 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art - The Harlem Connection, February 3, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "A Distant Country Called Youth,", June 11, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "The Producers,", July 2004 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Billy Budd,", October 2004 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Performing Arts Center - Montgomery College - Mickey Rooney - "The One Man One Wife Show with Jan Rooney,", October 23, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Jackie Mason, November 16, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Thoroughly Modern Millie,", December 7, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Theatre J - DCJCC (DC Jewish Community Center) - "The Tattooed Girl,", January 11, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - National Acrobats of Taiwan, March 2005 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Broadhurst Theatre - "700 Sundays" - Billy Crystal, April 2005 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Pan American Symphony Orchestra - "Todo Tango IV,", April 9, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - The Studio Theatre - "Take Me Out,", May 18, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Theatre J - DCJCC - "Central Park West/Riverside Drive,", June 25, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Theatre J - DCJCC - "The Disputation,", August 31, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Pan American Symphony Orchestra - "Tango Apiazzollado,", September 17, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Residence of H.E. Eva Nowotny, Josef Mayr and Ingrid Wagner-Kraft, September 21, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - National Building Museum - Presentation of the Vincent Scully Prize to His Royal Highness The Prince of Wales, November 3, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - The Studio Theatre - "Fat Pig,", January 4, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Washington Stage Guild - "An Empty Plate in the Cafe du Grand Boeuf,", January 5, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - National Theatre - "Dame Edna Back With A Vengeance,", March 2006 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - The Studio Theatre - "The Prime of Miss Jean Brodie,", March 8, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Theatre J - DCJCC - "Bal Masque,", April 5, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Pan American Symphony Orchestra - "Tango Tonight,", April 29, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Metro Stage - "Ellington: The Life of Music of The Duke,", July 14, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Pan American Symphony Orchestra - Tango Festival, September 14, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - National Theatre - "Legends!" Featuring Joan Collins and Linda Evans, November 2006 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Arena Stage - "She Loves Me,", November 17, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Metro Stage - "Bricktop,", January 17, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Walter Kerr Theatre - "Grey Gardens," Featuring Christine Ebersole, February 2007 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - National Theatre - "Doubt," Featuring Cherry Jones, March 2007 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Theatre J - DCJCC - "Family Secrets,", March 7, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Jazz at Lincoln Center Orchestra with Wynton Marsalis, March 13, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Metro Stage - "The Musical of Musicals,", April 17, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Pan American Symphony Orchestra - "Antologia del Tango,", May 5, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Signature Theatre "The Witches of Eastwick,", June 5, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Wolf Trap - Randy Travis, July 27, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - The Studio Theatre - "Red Light Winter,", September 6, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - The Hill Playhouse - "Porches,", circa 2000s (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - The Capitol Steps - "Who Put the Mock in Democracy?,", circa 2000s (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Lisner Auditorium - "Viva El Tango,", circa 2000s (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - "A Tuna Christmas,", circa 2000s (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Stage Magazine - "Forever Tango,", circa 2000s (Box 12, Folder 42)